As we all travel across the
sea Raising our voices We
take in the beautiful blue
world Our spirits ready to
go Everybody rejoices Now
let's go Get the sails all
yeah Here we are in between
the sea and the sky Ready
now for adventure We're
itching to try Get ready to
roll So all aboard now We're
set to go Set sail to the
ocean so deep Ready for a
truly grand adventure Well,
don't you think That sounds really
fun All this excitement Second to
none As we all travel across the sea
Raising our voices We take in the
beautiful blue world Our spirits ready
to go Everybody rejoices Now let's
go Get the cells all unfurled La la
yeah If there's something
that I just won't
ever forget It's the way that I felt when
our journey was set Now
I won't be scared As
long as I keep that
feeling there With that,
let us keep up the pace While
enjoying every trip from place to
place Our timid hearts get the
rhythm ingrained So let's keep going,
adventure awaits So many treasures
await So now let's raise our voices
in pride Laughing out when they are
found With all the riches in hand,
everybody rejoices Party on,
cause we stand tall and proud
Life is adventurous, be aware it's
dangerous Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mass.
Back to the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece!
Bring all your dreams with
you now, fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more!
So many treasures await.
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on!
Cause we stand tall and proud.
Disappearing!
Captain Lola!
Everyone!
We should have won!
Damn it!
Whoa!
Captain!
Captain, you need to come
onto the deck quickly!
You idiot.
We haven't seen the sun in two years
since Merde has stole our shadows.
Go back to sleep.
I know, Captain. But look!
Take a look at my feet!
Uh... Huh?
Your shadow.
It's...
I bet it's the same for you, Captain.
We got our shadows back!
All of us, Captain!
Every member of the crew
had their shadows returned!
Hey, Captain,
do you think this means someone out
there was able to beat Gecko Moria?
Oh, come on.
Like, that's bloody likely.
Even before Moria became a warlord,
he went toe-to-toe with Kaido
of the four pirate emperors.
Do you think someone came along
and was able to bring him down?
That's just crazy talk.
I got it back!
My shadow has returned!
It feels so good to see the sun again!
I don't know how, but our zombies
at Thriller Park must have died.
Patty, this curse has finally been lifted.
I can't believe it.
We can stand out the sunlight.
We have our shadows back again.
Look, they're following us.
My reflection.
I can see it.
What's all the fuss
about margarita my shadow
my shadow has returned after all this time
what It just returned
you said a pirate stole
it 10 years ago but
now it's back it's true
Master i'm so sorry i was so surprised when
i saw it i dropped your cherished plates
I've hated plates for
a long time now but all
of a sudden i seem to
have gotten over all that
I'm sorry to be so much
trouble I'll pack my
things and leave the
mansion right away Goodbye
Hold on
Now, what are you talking about?
Who cares about those silly old plates?
All that matters is
you weren't hurt, okay?
And now you have your shadow back.
I am so happy for you!
Sir?
Thank goodness that's over!
Look at that!
Guess it wasn't my day to die after all.
I thought I was on my way to
heaven for a moment there.
That sounds good to me.
It'd be like heaven.
Two times over.
If I was with you.
Stop laughing!
You jackasses!
Half your bodies were gone.
We Thought you were all dead.
Get a grip!
That was scary. Yeah. It's sunlight.
We don't have to be Afraid of it anymore.
We have our shadows back.
Our days of hiding in the
dark are finally over.
It looks like everybody survived.
The sunlight had definitely
begun to erase our existence.
But our shadows returned,
changing our bodies to their fully
recovered state just in time.
That would follow the same
logic as when we saw Moria
change the shape of Ours
by manipulating his shadow.
My theory is that the
shadow must know what
shape its owner is supposed
to be or something.
Hell if I know.
But relax, now that we beat Moria,
I don't think we'll
ever have to worry about
our shadows being stolen
away from us again.
I'm glad that's over,
and that no one or their shadow
ended up disappearing for good.
I don't know about you guys, but
all that fighting wore me out.
Has anybody got any cola?
All the creepy crap and weird creatures
in this place were an illusion.
A false reality made
by Moria and his crew.
Now that he's been beaten, there's
nothing left in this place.
It's like we all woke up from
the same horrible nightmare
and I for one I'm Sure as
hell glad it's over hey hey
Absalom wake up wake up
damn it hey come on wake up
would
you calm
down her shadows
already left her body dr.
Mr. Hogback?
What are you doing here,
and what happened to me?
How the hell should I
know what happened to you?
You probably got your ass kicked
in some embarrassing manner.
I wasn't here, but anyway, something
awful has happened to Master Meat!
What?!
Master Meat has been defeated
by Straw Hat Loopy! Shut up!
You're too damn loud!
Use your inside voice!
Your inside voice!
I'm pissed because Thriller
Bark is useless to me now.
But I have no intention of living out
the rest of my life as a washed-up loser!
How about you?
Wait, what do you mean?
Luffy got small again a second ago, huh?
He told me that when he uses third gear,
his body shrinks for a
while as a side effect.
These new fighting techniques seem
like too much for his body to handle.
He could actually hurt himself.
It's really starting to worry me.
Every enemy we run into is stronger
than the last one we faced.
He's gonna have to keep doing
this to himself every single time.
We need to pull ourselves
together, and soon.
Holy crap, it's a zombie!
One of them kept their shadows
even after we beat Moria!
No, I'm just an old man
with serious injuries.
That's too damn confusing!
Can't you just be a zombie?
Jeez!
Aren't you that old geezer
we met in the cemetery?
It's unbelievable to
think that we'd see the
day when we'd be able to
walk under the sun again
Thank you so much.
I don't know how we
can ever repay you Hey!
Oh, man, spoil!
Hey!
It's the honorary chairman
of the Victims Club!
Oh, well, look who it is.
You're all okay, then?
Yes. And you? Sure am.
Then I guess they all know
each other or something.
Good. You're all here.
I'm sorry we didn't thank you sooner.
We're really grateful to
every last one of you folks.
Sorry we got you all
wrapped up in our mess here.
Yeah, we knew it when we first saw you.
You were our only hope against Moria
and that damn curse he put on us.
So thank you all very much.
From me and all the members of
the Thriller Bark Victims Club.
We will never forget that
we owe you our lives.
Thank you from the bottom of our hearts.
If you ever need anything,
please let us know.
We may not have much, but all
we have is yours for the taking.
And lastly, and most importantly, I
will allow one of you to marry me.
Hell no!
There's really no need for
all this thank you stuff.
Who's it gonna be?
It's like Luffy told the
old man when we got here.
You?
Are you?
We were fighting for our own
crew and on our own terms.
Who's the lucky guy?
The fact that you guys were
rescued too is just a bonus.
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Someone was finally showing
us a little gratitude!
Yeah, she's right.
Let us thank you all proper-like, okay?
You guys might not have
set out to save us,
But we're still glad you
sent Merde a packing?
You are? Really?
I should have known.
Oh no, I forgot something
really important. What?
There's still another warlord on
the island Is something wrong?
Everyone, this is serious.
I see.
My greatest fears have become
an unfortunate reality.
So it would seem.
Whoa!
Who is that guy?
He's here.
Stay calm and listen. Please.
During the fight with
Moria and the others...
I forgot to tell you, but...
There's another one of them on the island.
One of the seven warlords of the sea!
Wait!
So he's...
one of...
The seven warlords of the sea!
Of course all of this happens just when we
finally chose a successor for Crocodile.
Losing another warlord in such
a short time sets a bad example.
Can you tell if he's still
breathing, even in the slightest? No.
If he is in fact still alive,
we will wait for his
recovery and hope he can
maintain his position as
one of the Seven Warlords.
We will follow up after such time comes.
The dignity of the
Warlords would be tarnished
if we were to keep losing them so easily.
It is critical that this
news not reach anyone else.
These damn Straw Hats are such a ducence.
It's him.
The man who stands just as tall as Moria.
The pirate known throughout
the world as the Tyrant.
Bartholomew Kuma. On away!
That's Tyrant Kuma!
I feel I've made my orders
quite clear on this matter.
We can not afford to let anyone
else know of Moria's defeat.
This is a direct order
from the world government.
Obliterate the Straw Hat crew and
everyone else on Thriller Bark.
Leave no one alive.
Simple enough.
Wait, did he just say
what I think he said?
He's gonna obliterate us?
They wanna kill all of us?
I don't understand.
What for?
Man, this cannot be happening.
We just managed to get all our shadows
back from Moria, and now this, too?
Oh, come on!
How many of these warlords
do we have to fight?
Everyone stand back.
I'll handle this.
Be careful.
He has some strange abilities.
I saw him make someone disappear.
With only a touch of his hand.
You mean like Pooh but
they're suddenly gone?
So scary.
And he can move from one location
to another in a split second!
Don't let him touch you.
It's dangerous.
He's right here!
And he's huge!
How'd he do that? Damn it all!
And just when we got our freedom back too!
There's no way I'm going
down now without a fight!
You think we're just gonna roll over and
die after all the crap we've been through?
You got another thing coming, pal!
Let's take him down! You heard him!
It's do or die!
Stop it, all of you!
This guy's way too strong!
Back off!
Even the ones he didn't touch, it's almost
like something shot right through them.
Pirate Hunter Zoro
Shall I begin the annihilation with you?
Come on hang in there
little buddy don't you die
on me what the hell did
that bastard just pull?
He knocked him out without laying a finger
on him what kind of
powers does this guy have?
What kind of sick twist
of fate is this all these
years we've spent hiding
in that dark forest?
Suffering beneath Merde is tyranny
and just when the nightmare seems
like it's over another one of The
seven warlords shows up and says
he's going to
annihilate us
this
guy's got no sense of honor He
knows the battle they just went
through and what kind of shape they're
in he's just kicking Them when
they're down screw the odds we may
not have their powers but we can
still fight So you're gonna have to
deal with us yeah who cares if you're
one of the seven warlords You're
nothing compared to oars and Merde
drop the big talk and stay back
I'm the one he called out
you heard it as well as i did
I'll give him the fight he wants you want
to talk about honor then don't butt in
Your crew's developed quite the popular
reputation, among scum, that is.
It seems that some of the tales
of your crew are true, though.
It's clear Straw Hat Luffy has staffed
his ship with rather skilled underlings.
Oh, no, no, no, stop it, really!
You're making me blush at you guys.
This is hardly the time
to be flattered, you guys!
You leave a trail of trouble
in your wake everywhere you go.
The infamy isn't reserved
for your captain.
You each bear your own
share of responsibility.
Don't do it, Zoro!
It's madness with the
state that you're in.
Your bones have got to be
nothing but dust at this point.
When disaster stares you down?
You've either got to step up or
just get the hell out of the way.
I prefer the former, making
excuses won't delay catastrophe.
If I die here and now, that's
as far as I was meant to go.
Two-sword style, draw!
Rossimon!
Holy crap, this guy's fast!
You see, Kuma didn't even touch
him and his breathing's all ragged!
What's his power?
I can't even figure out what he's doing!
Then what are those weird
marks left on the rubble?
his hand what's that on
his paw are those are they
paw pads that's crazy why
would a human have paw pads
36 caliber
phoenix look
out he deflected zoro's
attack with his bare hands
how is that even Impossible!
I think I just figured
out what your ability is.
I possess the power to
deflect anything I wish.
You see, I ate the pawpaw fruit
and became a pawpawmed human.
Uh, pawpawmed human?
Huh?
How can he say that with a straight face?
That's the most ridiculous
Devil Fruit I've ever heard of!
I'm not claiming that I know
much about these seven warlords.
But if this guy's power is kitten
hands, what are we worried about?
Franky, no!
Franky!
I'm disappointed, Cyborg Franky.
If that's the extent of your power,
you should keep your mouth shut.
It's just a theory.
But perhaps he's deflecting
the air itself a normal
physical attack wouldn't have
affected Franky like that.
I Call it the pad cannon.
I simply deflect to air
pressure at light speed and
it creates a shockwave that
can pierce through anything
I don't believe in mercy
Feel my thrust pad cannon!
Streaming wolf swords!
Zoro!
He can even repel his swords!
This is pointless!
There's no way he can keep going!
It's a miracle he's gone this
long in the condition he's in!
You saw the beating he took from Ores!
If this guy lays a finger
on him, he's done for!
Zoro!
Look behind you! Run!
That's as far as you'll get!
Konkase!
He didn't have a chance
to deflect his kick!
His skull's gonna be a thousand pieces!
Awesome!
Idiot, I said not to butt in!
I take it you're a black leg, Sanji.
I expected more from you.
He kicked him in the face
and he didn't even flinch.
This just keeps getting worse and worse.
What the hell?
Is his face made of steel?
That kick should have busted in his skull.
Go now, Phoenix Star!
The King of Sniper steps to the place,
a title you clearly gave yourself.
I knew from the start
that killing a crew of
injured weaklings like you
would bring me new joy.
Not to mention that it's not a fair
fight but orders are orders even
if I may not fully agree with them
what the hell is
he doing is that air
it looks like a giant bubble shaped
like a paw and he keeps making it
smaller I think I know what he's doing
he's using his power to deflect a
giant air mass but he's compressing
it into a tiny ball the real attack
will come as soon as he releases all
of that compressed pressure that much
air it'll send out a massive shock
wave like an enormous bomb did I hear
you right like a
bomb you mean he's
gonna release that and blow us all?
This is bad.
I've thought it over,
and I've made a decision.
I will spare your lives.
But on one condition!
In exchange for this act of magnanimity,
you give me the head of Straw Hat Luffy.
If I return with him, That should
be enough to satisfy the government.
We won't betray our own captain!
Never!
This was your choice.
Lines on!
Of course, I should have known.
You're a cyborg like Franky, huh?
Not quite, but made of
something tougher than he is.
A cyborg?
I suppose you could say that.
But my metal parts are all I have
in common with your friend, Franky.
I'm a creation known as a pacifista,
an in-development human weapons
project of the world government.
A pacifista?
I was created by the government's
most renowned scientist, Dr.
Vegabuck, one of the greatest
geniuses this world has ever known.
To put that into perspective,
his discoveries are so
sophisticated that it's believed it
will take the rest of the world
500 years to catch up to him.
Technology that advanced.
And you have Devil Fruit powers.
I'm starting to think.
You have an advantage over me.
Well this is embarrassing.
My body's shutting down.
You won't listen to me anymore.
The only way you'll back down
Is if we give you Luffy's head.
That is the only compromise.
I'm willing to offer.
You want a head Then I'll give you a head.
However, I can't give you my captains.
You'll have to take mine instead.
Please settle for that.
I may not have the same bounty on
my head as Luffy at the moment.
But I swear to you that
I am destined to become
the greatest swordsman
the world has ever known.
Surely that must be worth something.
You possess that much ambition.
And yet you're willing to give it all up.
and exchange your life for his?
The way things are looking, I don't see
any other way to save the rest of my crew.
What's the point of having ambition
if I can't even save my captain?
Luffy is the man who'll
become king of the pirates!
You're real cute.
Stop trying to show me up.
You got the right idea,
but what about your dream?
You can't accomplish anything if
you're dead, you stubborn fool.
Listen, you giant oaf.
Hey, don't bother with Mosshead here.
If you're taking a head, take mine.
The government might not consider
me a serious threat right now,
but you'll regret not taking my head
over his once I start making trouble.
Now's your chance to
take on Blackleg Sanji.
The only head you're taking is mine.
Forget about these fools!
Get out of here. Kill me!
I'm just as ready to
sacrifice myself as he is.
I fed people my whole life.
And now I'll feed the worms.
Hey, do me a favor.
Tell everyone I'm sorry
I couldn't say goodbye.
I hate to put you guys out.
But it looks like you'll
have to find a new cook.
Mosshead, you son of
Now show me you've got some honor.
You've made sure I can't
even touch Straw Hat?
Not unless I want to shame myself!
Then you've got my respect.
If that's what you want,
I give you my word.
I won't take Straw Hat's head.
But if you're intent on taking his place,
you will experience a living hell.
I've just repelled all physical injury
from Straw Hat's body, his exhaustion,
his pain.
What rests before you is the sum total of
anguish he endured during
his battle with Moria.
If you truly wish to take his place,
then you must accept and
inflict his agony upon yourself.
As close to death as you are already,
not only will it undoubtedly kill you,
it will do so painfully.
Why don't you have a taste?
Do you still want it?
Just let me pick the location.
He couldn't be anyone's son
but yours, could he, Dragon?
Hey, is everyone still alive?
Are you guys okay?
He must have just assumed we were all dead
after that explosion and left the island.
Which means that we won!
Stupid bombing! This hurts!
Aw, come on, you gotta be kidding me!
How are you bouncing around like that?
This is awesome!
My body feels as good as new!
I wonder why! Quit lying!
Calm down before you hurt yourself!
It's possible he took so much damage
to the brain it knocked him silly.
No way that guy just let us go!
Damn it, Saru, what'd you do?
That's him.
It really freaked me out there.
So, what happened to the warlord?
Where the hell did all
this blood come from?
Hey, are you still alive?
Where'd that paw guy go?
What in the hell happened here?
What happened here?
Nothing at all.